http://www.federalreserveeducation.org/siteinfo/privacy-policy

Personal Information
You may access and browse this website without disclosing your personal data.  The personal information that you choose to provide to us is voluntary.
Generally, any personal information collected via this website is for Bank use only. We do not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except when we have your permission or under the following circumstances:
When we retain the services of other Federal Reserve Banks, outside agents or third parties under contract with the Bank. Such personal information is only provided to and used by those parties in conjunction with the services they provide to the Bank.
When we are required to disclose personal information about you to government officials or otherwise as required by subpoenas, court orders, legal process, or other legal obligations and to establish or exercise our rights and defend against claims.
When we investigate, prevent or take action against illegal activities or suspected fraud.
Changes to this Policy
We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy.  If changes have been made, they will be reflected by a revised effective date posted at the end of this policy.
Updated February 2011
Information-Security
If you provide personal information, we will maintain this information according to the Bank’s usual strict security and confidentiality standards.  The safeguarding of personal information is important to the Bank.  While we endeavor to maintain the security of personal information in our possession, we cannot guarantee such security.  The Bank is in no way responsible for the security of personal information or any other information provided by you while the information is being communicated to the Bank via this website, through e-mail or otherwise.  Nor is the Bank responsible for safeguarding information that you provide to a third party.
Cookies
"Cookies" are small pieces of information attached to your browser by a website that you visit. Cookies are used to track usage patterns, traffic trends and customer behavior, as well as to record other information from the website. We may use cookies on this site to collect statistical information about our users in aggregate.  We perform analysis on our web server’s log files to identify, among other things, our site’s most popular pages, the browsers and operating systems most often used by our visitors, the sites and search engines that have referred visitors to our site, and the domains from which our users visit us.
This analysis does not involve personally identifiable information. It is used only for the purpose of helping us understand and better meet our audiences’ needs. Some aggregate website analysis is performed for us by Google Analytics (http://www.google.com/analytics/), and may involve the use of cookies set by Google. For Google’s Privacy Policy, see http://www.google.com/privacy.html.
You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept it or not. You can also set your browser to not accept cookies at all. If you do so, however, some areas of some sites may not operate properly.
Children
The Bank is concerned about protecting children's privacy. This website is not directed toward children under 13, and the Bank does not solicit personally identifiable information from children.  Children are discouraged from providing personal information and should always obtain parental consent before releasing personal information.
Links
This website contains links to other websites.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to any website operated by a third party, and the Bank is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Monitoring and Other Considerations
This website and the Bank’s firewall are subject to monitoring by Federal Reserve System personnel.  Any and all users expressly consent to such monitoring and are advised that any evidence of criminal activity may be provided to law enforcement officials.
If you do not agree with any portion of this policy, you have the right to exit and not continue the session.  However, if you do continue to remain on this website, you implicitly consent to this policy.
This site is a product of the Federal Reserve.
